Justin Palmer

GAME DEVELOPER / SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Kansas City, MO 64157

(816) 785-3435

Justp02@hotmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To use my knowledge and expertise of computers, and their languages, to continue my growth in the field of Game Design/Development by using my ability to communicate clearly and efficiently when articulating complex ideas to my managed employees, and other departments, allowing my team to achieve their daily goals and tasks accurately, and on time.

EDUCATION .

Full Sail University Winter Park, Florida (2019-2023)

- -Software Engineering--Game Development-
- Course Director Award given Jan 2021 for exceptional work and enthusiasm on projects

EXPERIENCE

May 2023 – Present Software Engineer • Lead Programmer • Xodius Studios

Aug 2022 - Present Mechanical Technician • Sub-Assembly • UltraSource LLC

Oct 2019 - May 2023 Game Development • Alumni • Full Sail University

KEY SKILLS -

- Unreal 4
- Blueprints
- Unity
- C++/C#
- MARS/MIPS Assembly
- Object Oriented

Programming

- Data Oriented Programming
- Agile (Scrum)
- Trello & Jira
- MySQL
- OpenGL / Vulkan Graphic API
- Microsoft Office

PROJECTS

Feb 2023 - Present

Forgotten Memories (UNREAL: PC/SteamDeck) -Lead Programmer

https://store.steampowered.com/app/2351360/Forgotten_Memories/

- **Cross-Platform Integration**
- Coordinate with 3D Artist, Narrative Designer, Dev team to troubleshoot bugs and logical errors in Blueprints & Code
- Setup and monitor weekly Scrum Boards using Jira

May 2022

Hoddsmimir (UNREAL: PC/Android) -

Lead Programmer

- Cross-Platform Integration and Controls for Differing Inputs
- Setup Enemy AI using NavMesh and Collider/RayCast Checks
- Setup and monitor weekly Scrum Boards using Trello

[References Available Upon Request]